<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<blogs>
<blog>
<title>Bellaroca Island</title><author>Wilmer Pascual</author><date>2023-05-07</date><content>An Island Luxury Resort
All 20 hectares of Bellarocca Island Resort and Spa are mountainous terrain, with its highest point at 114 meters above sea-level. To seasoned travelers, images of the picturesque island of Santorini in Greece will come into mind upon reaching the resort. Common to both are its rolling terrains and immaculate white buildings perched atop its cliffs: white structures that reflect the sun and contrast with the azure blue seas below.</content></blog><blog><title>White Beach Poctoy</title><author>Wilmer Pascual</author><date>2023-05-07</date><content>Poctoy White Beach, located in the coastal town of Torrijos in Marinduque, is one of the popular beaches in the Philippines. The beach features a kilometer stretch of fine white sand and pristine blue waters that is perfect for swimming and snorkeling. The place also gives a scenic view of Mount Malindig, the highest point in the province that is famous among beginner mountain climbers. 

In Poctoy White Beach, tourists are usually welcomed with a heartwarming custom called putong. It is a traditional song and dance ritual which involves the crowning of tourists with flowers by the locals.

Like most islands in the Philippines, Poctoy White Beach is also home to good seafood like yellowfin, squid, crabs, and shrimp, which are freshly sourced daily. For a fee, visitors can have these cooked to their liking in canteens near the shoreline.

Aside from hiking Mount Malindig and snorkeling, Poctoy White Beach is also a destination for camping and kayaking. Visitors may also enjoy island-hopping to Gaspar, Melchor, and Baltazar Islands, collectively known as Tres Reyes Islands or Three Kings Islands. </content>
</blog>
<blog><title>ang 500 bow</title><author>Jennelyn Encarnacion</author><date>2023-05-14</date><content>two fifthy plus two fifthy equals to paybhandred bow.</content></blog><blog><title>ang bebe rubik ko</title><author>Erica Ems</author><date>2023-05-14</date><content>wala lang so handsome heyyyy</content></blog><blog><title>250</title><author>Lyka Ramiro Murillo</author><date>2023-05-30</date><content>Capayang is a barangay in the municipality of Mogpog, in the province of Marinduque. Its population as determined by the 2020 Census was 1,499. This represented 4.34% of the total population of Mogpog.</content></blog><blog><title>Amoingon Beach</title><author>Vanessa Octa</author><date>2023-05-30</date><content>If you like gazing at corals and colorful schools of fish rather than swimming and grilling, then you shouldn’t miss Amoingon Beach in Marinduque. Its waters are so teeming with marine life that many would call it the snorkeling capital of Marinduque. Still, if you’re not a fan of marine life or anything like that, you can still have fun above the clear shallow waters of Amoingon Beach. Get some fresh air and sunshine outdoors, or rent the nearest transient house and inhale the smell of the sea every morning while jogging. </content></blog></blogs>
